taazi.com 2017-06-24

# Privacy Policy

At Taazi.com, we are fully dedicated to respecting your privacy and to protecting any information you agree on sharing with us. Your privacy and security are a priority and we make sure that all information provided by you is safe with us. The Privacy Policy is made to protect and respect the privacy of all visitors at Taazi.com and its main aim is to notify you about the way your personal data is being used. 

The Policy also explains how Taazi.com uses information. We take responsibility for your trust in us and hope that you would get an enthralling experience every time you visit us. 

Your privacy matters to us the most and for this purpose we would like to ask you to please take a moment to read our privacy policy to make sure that you understand and agree with it. 

**What is Taazi's concern in collecting your personal information?**

You are required to setup an account using either your email address or logging on via Facebook. This is done in order to provide you the best possible services by: 

  * Creating your automated User Profile 
  * Keeping track of your likes and interests and thereby making the recommendations for you that best suit your interests.
  * Keeping you well-informed of what your friends are up to and what music they are listening.
  * Providing you up to date information of your favorite artists and upcoming events and trends.
  * Providing information on any new and exciting offers so that you do not miss out on any of the fun at Taazi.com

You may submit any further information that you would like on your Taazi profile. However, please keep in mind that whatever information you update other than what we ask for would be public and anyone with a Taazi account can view it. 

**Is my information on Taazi being shared with anyone else?**

We take your privacy very seriously and own full responsibility to ensure the security of your personal information. Like all other websites that use personal information, Taazi's softwares and tools also use your information on a need to know basis to provide you with the services that best match your interests. We assure you that this information shall be fully confidential and would not be used for any other purposes. 

We are upgrading our website each day to provide you the best service possible. We are also increasing our linkages with third parties so that we can all collaborate to give you an online experience that you have never experienced before. For this purpose, we might ask you to give us more details or to trust us so we can share this information with the third parties. This would only be done once we have your full approval and we would never give your information to any third party without such approval. 

If you agree to receive updates from Taazi, it would allow us to keep you posted on all the recent happenings and latest services. You would receive emails from time to time informing you about new features or services to the Taazi website. We assure you that your email address would not be shared with other parties for any purpose. 

**What does Taazi do to protect my personal information?**

At Taazi, we do not only take physical but also technical and administrative measures to protect your privacy and to prevent your personal information from loss, theft, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. We employ the best systems and processes in place to ensure the safety of your information. This is done by effectively implementing: 

  * Industry accepted security measures to safeguard and protect your personal information.
  * Restricted employee access to databases containing personal information and confidentiality requirements for all employees at Taazi.
  * Limited access to third parties.

To be eligible to use Taazi, you must be above the age of 13. Any user below the age of 13 shall not be allowed to make an account with us. Taazi rejects the registration of any/all users aged below 13. 

**Internet Protocol ("IP") Addresses, cookies and other variables:**

As you log on to Taazi.com using your IP address, a cookie, also known as an HTTP cookie or browser cookie, is stored in your web browser while you are browsing a website. When you browse the same website in the future, the data stored in the cookie can be retrieved by the website to notify the website of your previous activity. This is the same for every website that uses user information. However, since we have promised to keep your information totally confidential, therefore our only purpose in this is to give you only relevant information. 

You can choose to enable or disable the cookies by changing your browser settings. This would allow you to accept or reject a cookie whenever it appears. However, we must say that rejecting a cookie would interfere with the functions and you may not be able to get the optimum services which were promising to you, otherwise. 

We may use third party service providers to only help us analyze certain online activities. For example, these service providers help us keep track of the updates of our online campaigns and analyze visitor activity on Taazi.com. We may permit these service providers to use cookies and other technologies to perform these services for Taazi. 

Many websites gather certain non-personal information automatically and store it in log files, including things like your IP addresses, browser type, Internet service provider, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. None of this information identifies you directly. Taazi.com may also enable this technology for use in ways that are commonly accepted by industry practice. 

**Message boards, chat rooms and instant messaging:**

In the event that Taazi launches community-based services such as message boards, blogs, shout box, instant messaging and other similar services, you should be aware that any information you share is visible to all other users. Please note that the information that you submit to one of these forums can be read, collected or used by other individuals to send you unsolicited messages. Taazi does not take responsibility for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums. You are solely responsible for any content that you post there, including, but not limited to, any personal information that you choose to reveal in these public forums. In using any of these services, you agree that you will not use them for any purpose that is unlawful or in violation of Taazi’s Terms and Conditions. Please note that Taazi may, in its sole discretion, monitor postings in these forums to assure that users are complying with the Taazi’s Terms and Conditions. 

**Acceptance of Taazi's Privacy Policy:**

By using the Taazi’s website, you consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information by Taazi.com in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

As Taazi grows, changes, and expands to suit your needs and preferences, we may need to modify, alter or otherwise update this privacy policy. When we make changes to this Privacy Policy we will notify you here, so we encourage you to review this Privacy Policy from time to time. We may also attempt to notify you of any such changes to our Privacy Policy via email or by placing a notice on our home page, but are not required to do so. 

If you have any questions, concerns or thoughts about the privacy of your personal information while using the Taazi website or this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us at Our Contact Page on our website.
